<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="ideology">
        <item>Plycism</item>
        <item>Vyhucism</item>
        <item>Arewosm</item>
        <item>Hycrocism</item>
        <item>Zowotism</item>
        <item>Beclysm</item>
        <item>Neoleeism</item>
        <item>Fokritism</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ideology_desc">
        <item>Plycitic ideology was born in Ewira in 1900 after the devastating independence war with Tableuina. Special place in constructing fundamentals fo this ideology took ruling dynasty Plicy. Plycism includes ideas of supremacy, spiritualism, statism and ultranationalism.</item>
        <item>Vyhucistic ideology was founded by gatryan political party names "VYHUCA" (Abbreviation which means in creole-gatryan "Freedom"). Eventually they took power after 1956 coup, and by their external influence spread the idea in the all world. Vyhucism includes radical acratia and anarchy ideas.</item>
        <item>Arewoistic ideology was described by Diviner Sheherbaraz Arewo, the establisher of Wryzority, in the Far Adus Mountains in 16th century. Arewosm includes ideas of theocratic ruling, isolationism, reactionary conservatism.</item>
        <item>Hycrocism ideology was described by west-efraitian writer and revolutionist Kazimierz Chajka, whose pseudonym is "Hycro" (in efraitian means "Hammer") in 1913 in his book "New Way. The Second Part (with comments), which was zowotic "New Way" but with few additions and antitheses. Hycrocism includes agrarianism, autocracy and radical egalitarianism.</item>
        <item>Zowotism ideology was described by triarian politician Josiah Morrison in the second part autobiographical book "New Way" ("Novea Zowa" in triarian language). Zowotism includes sindicalism, nationalism and egalitarianism.</item>
        <item>Firstly Beclysm ideology was founded by Castelandish politicians, who fully supported reforms of the president Alan Becly. Beclysm includes liberalism, meritocracy and humanism.</item>
        <item>Leeism ideology was appeared in 1879 by aristocratic club "Lee Mates" in Cliutho Empire. Today Leeism is pretty archaic and it was replaced by its newer version - Neo-Leeism, which was promoted by Esnanan ruler Hanibal Philippou. Neoleeism includes conservatism, protectionism and traditionalism.</item>
        <item>Fokritism ideology was described by famous bochiunian scientist Amazat Fokrit in his magnus opus "Better vision". Fokritism includes technocracy, totalitarism and anti-globalism.</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>